# Kai Schuyler Gonzalez

Boulder, Colorado • (720) 496-5000 • linkedin.com/in/kaischuyler • kaischuyler.com

## **Software Engineer**

I am a software engineer with 2+ years of experience computer graphics. Through personal and professional projects, as well as relevant coursework and strong 3D math skills, I have a well-rounded view of the computer graphics field. I have experience with tools including Unity and Unreal, as well as experience in modern graphics APIs including OpenGL and shading languages like GLSL.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# CU Boulder Office of the Registrar • Boulder, Colorado • 06/2021 - 01/2022

## **Student Software Developer**

- Wrote software to assist with internal functions, mainly in the .NET framework using C#.
- Wrote multiple selenium applications that automated tasks for the office.
- Updated, debugged and documented legacy code used by the office.

#### **UCAR** • Boulder, Colorado • 08/2021 - 05/2022

## **CU Boulder Capstone Project**

- I worked alongside 6 other students and a project sponsor to create a web application over the course of 2 semesters.
- Lead exercises such as sprint planning and team standups.
- Kept the team on track to meet project deadlines on time.
- Communicated with sponsor to keep them updated on the status of the project.

## CU Boulder Environmental Center • Boulder, Colorado • 10/2019 - 12/2020

## **Student Transportation Ambassador**

- Assisted in the day to day internal operations of the office, mainly in the public transportation department.
- Helped organize the Environmental Center's ski bus for students.
- Promoted sustainability events and services on campus through multiple outreach programs.

# **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Science - BS in Computer Science**

University of Colorado Boulder • Boulder, Colorado • 07/2018 - 08/2022

#### **SKILLS**

OpenGL, C / C++, C#, CSS, Git, HTML, iOS SDK, JavaScript / Typescript, Node.js, Python, React.js, SQL, Swift, Unity